Guide to the Clark E. Warburton papers, 1920-1979
George Mason University Libraries
- Clark Warburton Papers
  - Cagan, Phillip and Schwartz, Anna J. "How Feasible is a Flexible Monetary Policy." (Folder 20, Box 68)
  - Caskey, Wayne F. (Folder 21, Box 68)
  - Catchings, Waddill and Ross, Charles F. (Folder 22, Box 68)
  - Lester, Chandler V. (Folder 23, Box 68)
  - Cole, Arthur H. (Folder 24, Box 68)
  - Copeland, Morris A. (Folder 25, Box 68)
  - Cortney, Philip (Folder 26, Box 68)
  - Dauer, Ernst A. (Folder 27, Box 68)
  - Deeds, Allan K. (Folder 28, Box 68)
  - Dublin, Jack (Folder 29, Box 68)
  - Eaton, Marquis G. (Folder 30, Box 68)
  - Edwards, George W. (Folder 31, Box 68)
  - "Economic Expansion and the American Banking System", Journal of Business, vol. XXIX, No.2, April 1956, Crutchfield, James A. and Hald, Earl C. (Folder 32, Box 68)
  - Walter, Egle (Folder 33, Box 68)
  - Ensley, Grover WM. (Folder 34, Box 68)
  - Allais, M."Explanation of the Economic Cycles." (Folder 35, Box 68)
  - Ezekiel- Tables from paper on Distribution of Gains from Rising Technical Efficiency in Progressing Economies. (Folder 36, Box 68)
  - Foulke, Roy A. (Folder 37, Box 68)
  - Fels, Rendigs (Folder 38, Box 68)
  - Fetter, Frank W. (Folder 39, Box 68)
  - Fisher, Irving (Folder 40a, Box 68)
  - Friedman, Milton (Folder 40b, Box 68)
  - Bratter, Herbert M. (Folder 41, Box 68)
  - H.J. Davenport: Effective Demand Before Keynes. (Folder 42, Box 68)
  - Alchian, Armen A. and Klein, Benjamin."On a Correct Measure of Inflation." (Folder 43, Box 68)
  - Friedman, Milton. "The Role of Monetary Policy." (Folder 44, Box 68)
  - Papers by Robert Black. (Folder 45, Box 68)
  - Cargill, Thomas F. (Folder 46, Box 68)
  - Latane, Henry A., "An Inter-Country Comparison of Interest Rates and Income Velocity." (Folder 1, Box 69)
  - Mayer, Tomas, "Consumption in the Great Depression", "Financial Guidelines and Credit Controls", "The Federal Reserve's Policy Procedures", "Our Financial Institutions", and "The Explanation of Excess Reserves in the 1930's." (Folder 2-6, Box 69)
  - Lerner, Eugene. "Money, Prices and Wages in the Confederacy, 1861-1865." (Folder 7, Box 69)
  - Funk, David G. (Folder 8, Box 69)
  - Fisher, Irving (Folder 9, Box 69)
  - Means, Gardiner C. (Folder 10, Box 69)
  - Golembe, Carter H. (Folder 11, Box 69)
  - Goodbar, Joseph E. (Folder 12, Box 69)
  - Gourvitch, Alexander (Folder 13, Box 69)
  - Gage, Lyman J. (Folder 14, Box 69)
  - Gideonse, Harry D. "The Commodity Dollar." (Folder 15, Box 69)
  - Gillmore, Curry W. (Folder 16, Box 69)
  - Girton, Lance and Roper, Don E. "James Lawrence Laughlin (Anti-Quantity Theorist) and the Monetary Approach to the Balance of Payments." (Folder 17, Box 69)
  - Hamilton, Earl J. (Folder 18, Box 69)
  - Rammond, Bray (Folder 19, Box 69)
  - Hart, Albert G. (Folder 20, Box 69)
  - Harwood, E.C. (Folder 21, Box 69)
  - Haymes, Harmon H. (Folder 22, Box 69)
  - Haywood, Charles F. (Folder 23, Box 69)
  - Herring, John P. (Folder 24, Box 69)
  - Hodgman, Donald R. (Folder 25, Box 69)
  - Houghton, Harrison F. (Folder 26, Box 69)
  - Latane, Henry A.- Income Velocity of Money and Interest Rates. (Folder 27, Box 69)
  - Jacobsson, Per (Folder 28, Box 69)
  - Jackson, Brown J.T. - Origin of the Dual Banking System. (Folder 29, Box 69)
  - James, Cyril F. (Folder 30, Box 69)
  - Jay, Pierre- Federal Reserve Operations. (Folder 31, Box 69)
  - Jenkins, H.P.B. (Folder 32, Box 69)
  - Johnson, Harry G. (Folder 33, Box 69)
  - The Journal of Economic History. (Folder 34, Box 69)
  - Karsten, C.F.- European Giro System. (Folder 35, Box 69)
  - Kemmerer, Donald L. (Folder 36, Box 69)
  - Kindahl, James K. (Folder 37, Box 69)
  - King, Willford I.- Business Cycles. (Folder 38, Box 69)
  - Klein, Lawrence R.- Econometrics of Consumption. (Folder 39, Box 69)
  - Kolesnikoff, Vladimir S.- Standard Classification of Industries in the United States. (Folder 40, Box 69)
  - Lerner, Eugene M.- Monetary Matters of American Civil War. (Folder 41, Box 69)
  - Legueu, F. F.- Question of Gold in France. (Folder 42, Box 69)
  - Lindow, Wesley- Monetary and Financial Statistics. (Folder 43, Box 69)
  - Long, Clarence D. - Impact of Effective Demand on the Labor Supply. (Folder 44, Box 69)
  - Lough, William H.- Commercial and Financial Chronicle. (Folder 45, Box 69)
  - Lucking, Alfred W. (Folder 46, Box 69)
  - Lanston, Aubrey G.- A Critique of the Eckstein Report Etcetera. (Folder 47, Box 69)
  - Leffingwell, R.C. (Folder 48, Box 69)
  - Leong, Y.S.- The Physical Volume Production of Producers' and Consumers' Goods. (Folder 49, Box 69)
  - Jackson, William D.- Atlantic Economic Conference. (Folder 50, Box 69)
  - Mayer, Thomas - Policy in Less Developed Countries. (Folder 51, Box 69)
  - McEvoy, Raymond H.- Federal Reserve. (Folder 52, Box 69)
  - McKean, Roland N.- Liquidity and a National Balance Sheet. (Folder 53, Box 69)
  - Macesich, George- Inflation (Folder 54, Box 69)
  - Mack, Ruth P.- Inflation and Costs. (Folder 55, Box 69)
  - Manuel, Ralph W.- Banking. (Folder 56, Box 69)
  - Mao, James C.T. (Folder 57, Box 69)
  - Marschak, Jacob- Role of Liquidity. (Folder 58, Box 69)
  - May, George O.- Business Income. (Folder 59, Box 69)
  - Mason, Edward S.- "Foreign Money We Can't Spend." (Folder 60, Box 69)
  - Meltzer, Allan H.- Money Demand. (Folder 62, Box 69)
  - Mints, Lloyd W.- Monetary Policy. (Folder 63, Box 69)
  - Mints, Lloyd W.- Symposium on Fiscal and Monetary Policy. (Folder 64, Box 69)
  - Mendershausen, Horst- Economic Time Series. (Folder 65, Box 69)
  - McCracken, Paul W.- 1953 Business Picture. (Folder 66, Box 69)
  - Mitchell, George W.- Monetary System. (Folder 67, Box 69)
  - Mayer, Thomas- Proposal for a Graduated Deposit Insurance Plan. (Folder 68, Box 69)
  - Modigliani, Franco- Interest and Money. (Folder 69 a, Box 69)
  - Modigliani, Franco and Ando, Albert K.- Savings. (Folder 69 b, Box 69)
  - The Monetary Standards Inquiry. (Folder 70, Box 69)
  - Mott, Howard S.- The Problem of Prices. (Folder 71, Box 69)
  - National Industrial Conference Board- Gold Standard. (Folder 72, Box 69)
  - National Planning Association- The Stakes of Bretton Woods. (Folder 73, Box 69)
  - Institute of International Finance- Monetary Policy and Employment. (Folder 74, Box 69)
  - Latane, Henry A.- Portfolio Balance. (Folder 75, Box 69)
  - Peake, Charles F.- Major Issues in Monetary Economics. (Folder 76, Box 69)
  - Patman, Wright- Congressional Policy in the Financial Field. (Folder 77, Box 69)
  - Peake, Charles F.- Historical Lessons Suggesting the Desirability of an International Money and Central Bank. (Folder 78, Box 69)
  - Pabst Postwar Employment Awards. (Folder 79, Box 69)
  - Palyi, Melchior- Inter-bank Balances. (Folder 80, Box 69)
  - Pfouts, R.W.- Theory of Distribution. (Folder 81, Box 69)
  - Pearson, F.A.- Farm Economics. (Folder 82, Box 69)
  - Pittman, Key- The World Silver Problem. (Folder 83, Box 69)
  - Polakoff, Murray E.- Discount Theory and Policy. (Folder 84, Box 69)
  - Prettyman, Claude B.- Depression. (Folder 85, Box 69)
  - Mayer, Thomas- The Structure and Operation of The Federal Reserve System. (Folder 86, Box 69)
  - Hon. Carter Glass- Truth About the Federal Reserve System. (Folder 87, Box 69)
  - Latane, Henry- The Income Velocity of Money, Long-Term Interest Rates and Returns. (Folder 88, Box 69)
  - Mayer, Thomas- Income Theory. (Folder 89, Box 69)
  - William, Pole- Money Growth During Business Cycle Expansion. (Folder 90, Box 69)
  - Tyng, Ed- Open Market Operations. (Folder 1, Box 70)
  - Economic Forum Held by The Society for Stability in Money and Banking. (Folder 2, Box 70)
  - Yeager, Leland B. - The Keynesian Diversion. (Folder 3, Box 70)
  - Raushenbush, Stephen- Productivity and Employment. (Folder 4, Box 70)
  - Rosenson, Alex Moses- Monetary Effects of Wartime Social Security Taxes. (Folder 5, Box 70)
  - Rothschild, K.W.- Public Expenditure in the National Income: A Note. (Folder 6, Box 70)
  - Ruml, Beardsley and Sonne H. Chr.- Fiscal and Monetary Policy. (Folder 7, Box 70)
  - Ross, Charles F.- Business Indexes and Stock Prices. (Folder 8, Box 70)
  - Reynolds, Lloyd G.- Producers' Goods Prices in Expansion and Decline. (Folder 9, Box 70)
  - Riddle, J.H. (Folder 10, Box 70)
  - Reuther, Walter P.- Price Policy and Public Responsibility. (Folder 11, Box 70)
  - Reierson, Roy L. (Folder 12 a, Box 70)
  - Sickle, J.V. Van- Reform of Federal Taxes on Personal and Corporate Income. (Folder 12 b, Box 70)
  - Singh, Ranbir- Rural Cooperative Banking Systems for Short-Term and Intermediate Credit in Canada, United States, and The Union of South Africa. (Folder 13, Box 70)
  - Simmons, Edward C.- The Gold Certificate, Elasticity of The Federal Reserve Note, The Concept of Lawful Money, Borrowing by Federal Reserve Banks, Banking and Capital Accumulation, An Analysis of Factors Affecting the Volume of Currency in Circulation, and Secondary Reserve Requirements for Commercial Banks. (Folder 14, Box 70)
  - Simons, Henry C.- Some Reflections on Syndicalism. (Folder 15, Box 70)
  - Slichter, Sumner H.- Slow Inflation, Retirement Age and Social Policy, and The Business Outlook. (Folder 16, Box 70)
  - Smith, W.L.- Interest and Money in Macrodynamic Models. (Folder 17, Box 70)
  - Snyder, Carl (Folder 18, Box 70)
  - Krech, Alvin W.- Currency Inflation and Public Debts, 1921. (Folder 19, Box 70)
  - Severson, Harry L.- Valuation of Bank Assets and "Going Concern Value" in Bank Examination. (Folder 20, Box 70)
  - Schapiro, M.A.- The Triple Banking System. (Folder 21, Box 70)
  - Schotta, Charles Jr.- Open Market Operations. (Folder 22, Box 70)
  - Schur, Leon M. "The Second Bank of the United States and the Inflation After the War of 1812." The Journal of Political Economy, vol.LXVIII, No.2, April, 1960. (Folder 23, Box 70)
  - Selden, Richard T. "Cost-Push Versus Demand Pull Inflation, 1955-57." The Journal of Political Economy, Vol.LXVII, No.1, February, 1959. (Folder 24, Box 70)
  - Speagle, Richard E. and Kohn, Ernest. "Employment and Output in Banking, 1919-1955." The Review of Economics and Statistics, vol.XL, No.1, February, 1958. (Folder 25, Box 70)
  - Spengler, Joseph H. (Folder 26, Box 70)
  - Steiner, W.H. "South Carolina Cash Depositories." The Southern Economic Journal, Vol.IV, No.1, July, 1937. (Folder 27, Box 70)
  - Stern, Ernest H.- Inflationary Potential and Prices, Capital Requirements in Progressive Economies, The Problem of Capital Accumulation, and The Pattern of Sterling Area Payments. (Folder 28, Box 70)
  - Stewart, W.W- Monetary Policy and Economic Prosperity. (Folder 29, Box 70)
  - Stigler, George J.- Social Welfare and Differential Prices. (Folder 30, Box 70)
  - Sumner, John D.- Public Utility Prices and the Business Cycle: A Study in the Theory of Price Rigidity. (Folder 31, Box 70)
  - Triffin, Robert- The Threat to the Dollar. (Folder 32, Box 70)
  - Turner, Robert C.- Lectures on Economic Growth. 5-15-60 (Folder 33, Box 70)
  - Tucker, Rufus S.- Distribution of Tax Burdens in 1948. (Folder 34, Box 70)
  - Townsend, David (Folder 35, Box 70)
  - Tobin, James- Liquidity Preference, Monetary Policy. (Folder 36, Box 70)
  - Timberlake, Richard H.- The Specie Standard and Central Banking in the U.S. before 1860. (Folder 37, Box 70)
  - Thompson, Donald S.- Analysis of the Twenty-Fifth Annual Report of the FR Board, 1938. (Folder 38, Box 70)
  - Terborgh, George- Public and Private Investment After the War. 11-23-43 (Folder 39, Box 70)
  - Taylor, Charles T.- Southern Versus Non-Southern Underwriting of Municipals (FR Bank of Atlanta). (Folder 40, Box 70)
  - Uhr, Carl G.- Knut Wicksell's Role in the Development of Mathematical Economics. (Folder 41, Box 70)
  - Statistics of National Income and Expenditure- United Nations. (Folder 42, Box 70)
  - Upgren, Arthur R.- Life Insurance and Inflation. (Folder 43, Box 70)
  - Viner, Jacob- Full Employment, Banking, Laissez Faire. (Folder 44, Box 70)
  - Voorhis, Jerry- Prevent Inflation and Deflation and Answer America's Debt Problem. (Folder 45, Box 70)
  - Wallace, Henry- I Said 1950-I Meant It. (Folder 46, Box 70)
  - Fels, Bruno and Whelpton, P.K.- An Industrial Classification for Reports From Individuals. (Folder 47, Box 70)
  - Wichmann, Arthur A.- India's Economic Problems, The Federal Debt, A Reexamination of Discriminatory Price Practices. (Folder 48, Box 70)
  - Williams, John H.- The Task of Economic Recovery, An Appraisal of Keynesian Economics. (Folder 49, Box 70)
  - Wilson, C.E.- Gold-- Just Another Commodity. (Folder 50, Box 70)
  - Woytinsky, W.S.- Two More Contributions on the Consumption Function, Review (Economics and Statistics). (Folder 51, Box 70)
  - Yasui, Takuma- Non-linear Self-excited Oscillations and Business Cycles. (Folder 52, Box 70)
  - Yntema,Theodore O.-Subcommittee on Antitrust and Monopoly of the Committee on the Judiciary, United State Senate. Finance, Ford Motor Company. (Folder 53, Box 70)
  - Addresses at National Economists Club. (Folder 1, Box 71)
  - American Economic Association, 1974. (Folder 2, Box 71)
  - Atlantic Economic Conference. (Folder 3, Box 71)
  - Southern Economic Association. (Folder 4, Box 71)
  - Business Cycle Theory and the Hayek-Kaldor Controversy About the Ricardo Effect, Factors Affecting Adequacy of Demand For Potential Postwar Output, Forecasting With Statistical Indicators, The Rise and Decline of Business Cycle Theory, The Purely Monetary Theory of Business Cycles in Classical Economics, Modes of Rationality. (Box 71)
  - Papers of the Sixth Annual Conference of the History of Economics Society, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, Volumes 1-2, May 23-26, 1979. (Box 71)
  - ASSA- Chicago, August 1978. (Folder 1, Box 72)
  - ASSA- John Atlee's paper, Chicago, August 1978. (Folder 2, Box 72)
  - ASSA- Wilson's and Ronk's Papers, Chicago, 1978. (Folder 3, Box 72)
  - Yeager, Leland B.- What Are Banks?, October 1977. (Folder 4, Box 72)
  - Southern Economic Association, August 1978. (Folder 5, Box 72)
  - Southern Economic Association, November 1978. (Folder 6, Box 72)
  - Conference on Research in Income and Wealth, May 1979. (Folder 7, Box 72)
  - Conference on Reserve Requirements and the Role of Federal Reserve System. (Folder 1, Box 73)
  - Individual Taxes and the Distribution of Income. 11-3-72 (Folder 2, Box 73)
  - Conference on Research in Income and Wealth- Ohio University, University of Essex, The Pennsylvania State University. 10-3-72, 10-4-72 (Folder 3, 9, 10, Box 73)
  - Conference on Personal Distributions of Income and Wealth- Pennsylvania State University. 10-3-72, 10-4-72 (Folder 5, Box 73)
  - Appendix A (Folder 6, Box 73)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare. (Folder 7, Box 73)
  - Notes From NBER Conference on Research in Income and Wealth- State College, Pa. 10-3-72, 10-4-72 (Folder 8, Box 73)
  - Measurement of Transfer Income in the Current Population Survey. (Folder 11, Box 73)
  - Conference on Research in Income and Wealth- Pennsylvania State University, University of Michigan, State University of New York at Buffalo, Northwestern University. 11-4-71, 11-5-71, 11-6-71, 10-12-71, 11-6-59, 11-7-59 (Folder 1, 2, 8, 13, 14, 20, 21, Box 74)
  - Conference on the Measurement of Economic and Social Performance. 11-4-71, 11-5-71, 11-6-71 (Folder 5-6, Box 74)
  - Social Accounting for Transfer. (Folder 3, Box 74)
  - An Analysis of the Uniform Consumer Credit Code. (Folder 4, Box 74)
  - Measuring Social and Economic Change. (Folder 7, Box 74)
  - Basic Arithmetic of Income Redistribution. (Folder 9, Box 74)
  - Income Instability Amoung Young and Middle-Aged Men. (Folder 10, Box 74)
  - NBER (Folder 11, Box 74)
  - Monetary Change and Velocity in a Keynesian Model. (Folder 12, Box 74)
  - Banking in Prosperity. (Folder 15, Box 74)
  - Seminar on Manpower Policy and Program. (Folder 16, Box 74)
  - Bank for International Settlements. (Folder 17, Box 74)
  - Financial Resources in Century III. (Folder 18, Box 74)
  - Conference on Research in Income and Wealth - University of Rochester, Johns Hopkins University, University of British Columbia. (Folder 1-4, Box 75)
  - Appendix to the taxation of income. (Folder 5, Box 75)
  - Estimation of Capital Stock in the United States. (Folder 6, Box 75)
  - The Rise of a Managerial Economics. (Folder 7, Box 75)
  - The History of Economics Society. (Folder 8, Box 75)
  - Estimation of Capital Stock in the United States. (Folder 9, Box 75)
  - Core, Demi-Core Interaction (Folder 10, Box 75)
  - Applying the Philosophy of Science to the Philosophy of Economic Analysis. (Folder 11, Box 75)
  - Newton Versus Darwin in 19th Century Economics. (Folder 12, Box 75)
  - Smith and Hutton at Edinburg. (Folder 13, Box 75)
  - Hayek's and his students perceptions of the Keynesian revolution. (Folder 14, Box 75)
  - Two Traditions of Classical Monetary Theory: A Reconciliation. (Folder 15, Box 75)
  - Claude Menard- University of Paris. (Folder 16, Box 75)
  - Marxian and Ricardian Economics. (Folder 17, Box 75)
  - Clark Warburton and the Emergence of Monetarism. (Folder 18, Box 75)
  - The Transaction as the Integrating Concept in Understanding Twenty-Five Years of Monetary Theory. (Folder 19, Box 75)
  - Liberalist Economic Thought on the Role of Unions in Inflation. (Folder 20, Box 75)
  - American Economists and the High Cost of Living. (Folder 21, Box 75)
  - The History of Humanistic Economics. (Folder 22, Box 75)
  - Cosmopolitanism Versus the National Economy. (Folder 23, Box 75)
  - An Institutional Approach to Economic Inquiry in Catherinian Russia. (Folder 24, Box 75)
  - The (IR) Rationality of Discounting the Future. (Folder 25, Box 75)
  - Arthur Hadley's Analysis of Differential Railway Rates and the Theory of the Firm. (Folder 26, Box 75)
  - A Master Paradigm for Analyzing Historical Development of Economics. (Folder 27, Box 75)
  - Good Work and Bad: How Economic Thought Progresses. (Folder 28, Box 75)
  - The Time Preference Theory of Interest Rate Determination. (Folder 29, Box 75)
  - History of Economics Society Annual Conference. (Folder 30, Box 75)
  - Cambridge Versus Cambridge Controversies in Marx's Capital Theory. (Folder 31, Box 75)
  - Further Neglected Aspects of Leon Walras's Theoretical Writings. (Folder 32, Box 75)
  - The Pareto Principle. (Folder 33, Box 75)
  - Marshallian Economics. (Folder 34, Box 75)
  - Evolution of Profit Theory. (Folder 35, Box 75)
  - On Teaching the History of Economics. (Folder 36, Box 75)
  - An Appraisal of Current History of Economic Thought Text Books. (Folder 37, Box 75)
  - Translations: A Neglected Source. (Folder 38, Box 75)
  - The Simple Politics of Distributional Preference. (Folder 1, Box 76)
  - The Distributional Implications of National Air Pollution Damage Estimates. (Folder 2, Box 76)
  - Conference on Research in Income and Wealth- University of Pennsylvania, Bowdoin College, Michigan State University, University of Michigan, University of Virginia, NBER, New York University, University of Maryland, University of California, The Urban Institute, Harvard University, and Stanford University. 5-15-75, 5-16-75, 5-17-74, 11-21-74, 11-22-74, 11-23-74, 10-8-74 (Folder 3, 4, 5, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 16, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, Box 76)
  - Conference on the Distribution of Economic Well Being. (Folder 6, Box 76)
  - Price and Wage Behavior in the U.S. Aggregate Economy. (Folder 13, Box 76)
  - The Effect of Phases I, II, III on Wages, Prices, and Profit Margins. (Folder 14, Box 76)
  - Measurement and Price Effects of Aggregate Supply Constraints. (Folder 15, Box 76)
  - Canadian Experience With Recent Inflation. (Folder 17, Box 76)
  - Price Linkage in an Interdependent World Economy. (Folder 18, Box 76)
  - Memo 6-5-73 (Folder 19, Box 76)
  - An Analysis of Ghetto Housing Prices Overtime. (Folder 21, Box 76)
  - Federal Reserve Papers- SEA Conference. (Folder 1, Box 77)
  - FDIC Conference, May,1967. (Folder 2, Box 77)
  - Programs From SEA Conferences, 1962-63. (Folder 3, Box 77)
  - Handwritten lecture notes. (Folder 1, Box 78)
  - Lectures on Types of Economic Theory by Wesley C. Mitchell. (Folder 2-5, Box 78)
  - Willis- Outlines. (Folder 6, Box 78)
  - Lectures on Money and Banking, 1939-40 by Charles O. Hardy. (Box 78)
  - Annual Reports 1957-64 - Galley Proofs. (Folder 2-26, Box 79)
  - Memoranda, March 1936- December 1947. (Folder 1-120, Box 80)
  - Memoranda- Index 1934-1964. (Folder 1, Box 81)
  - Memoranda- January 1934- February 1936. (Folder 2-13, Box 81)
  - Correspondence July 1943- December 1965. (Folder 14-166, Box 81)
  - Correspondence January 1940-January 1941. (Folder 1-25, Box 82)
  - Correspondence October 1942- June 1943. (Folder 34-42, Box 82)
  - Annual Reports, 1954-1956- Drafts, indexes, and various parts. (Folder 1-17, Box 83)
  - Annual Report 1942- Preliminary Drafts. (Folder 1, 2, Box 84)
  - Annual Report 1943- Material from other divisions, memoranda, examination analysis. (Folder 3, 4, 5, Box 84)
  - Annual Report 1944- Materials from other divisions, memoranda, organization chart, preliminary draft of policy section, preliminary drafts of parts I-V, and Earning and Dividends (Parts I-III). (Folder 6-15, Box 84)
  - Annual Report 1945- Miscellaneous, memoranda, and materials from other divisions. (Folder 16-19, Box 84)
  - Annual Report 1946- Miscellaneous, materials from other divisions, original tables, and parts I-IV. (Folder 20-26, Box 84)
  - Annual Report 1950- Original tables, parts I-IV. (Folder 27-31, Box 84)
  - Annual Report 1947- Materials from other divisions, and tables. (Folder 1-3, Box 85)
  - Annual Report 1948- Articles on inflationary gap, materials from other divisions, and auditions report. (Folder 4-9, Box 85)
  - Annual Report 1949- Original tables. (Folder 10, 11, Box 85)
  - Annual Report 1950- Materials from other divisions. (Folder 12, 13, Box 85)
  - Annual Report 1951- Original material, progress reports, copy of charts, draft and data, and work papers. (Folder 14-20, Box 85)
  - Annual Report 1952- Work papers, list of names, special materials, materials from other divisions, and original tables. (Folder 1-7, Box 86)
  - Annual Report 1953- Drafts I-V, memos and correspondence, and other work papers. (Folder 8-21, Box 86)
  - Annual Report 1954- Parts I-III (memorandum and correspondence), Earnings section, and other work papers. (Folder 23-28, Box 86)
  - Correspondence January 1934- December 39. (Folder 1-59, Box 87)
  - Total Deposits. (Folder 60, Box 87)
  - Memoranda January 1956- December 1965. (Folder 61-101, Box 87)
  - Memorandum January 1953- December 1955. (Folder 1-35, Box 88)
  - Payments to creditors by national banks placed in receivership during 1921-30 excluding banks paying 100% or more on claims, or restored to solvency. Prepared by Mark D'Elia and Clark Warburton, October 1940- January 1941. (Folder 1, Box 89)
  - 299 national banks suspended during 1921-33 and reopened, succeeded or taken over. (Folder 2, Box 89)
  - 698 national banks suspended during 1921-33 and reopened, succeeded, or taken over. (Folder 3, Box 89)
  - 760 state banks suspended during 1921-33, and reopened or taken over. (Folder 4, Box 89)
  - 2,713 national banks suspended during 1921-33 and reopened by related states according to available sample for state banks. (Folder 5a, Box 89)
  - 3,364 state banks suspended during 1921-33 and reopened, succeeded, or taken over. (Folder 5b, Box 89)
  - 2,584 state banks suspended during 1921-33 and permanently closed for which liquidation data never available. (Folder 6, Box 89)
  - 1,716 national banks suspended during 1921-33 and permanently closed. (Folder 7, Box 89)
  - 8,730 state banks suspended during 1921-33 and permanently closed. (Folder 8, Box 89)